certifiedprofile.com 2013-09-26

# Privacy Policy | CP

## CertifiedProfile Privacy Policy

Click here for the CertifiedProfile Privacy Policy applicable to residents of Canada

Welcome to CertifiedProfile. By accessing and using CertifiedProfile and its services and network (the "Website"), you certify that you have read, understand, and agree to this Privacy Policy ("Privacy Policy"), whether or not you are a registered account ("Account") holder (registered and nonregistered Account holders collectively, "User" or "Users"). The Website is owned, operated, and administered by CertifiedBackground, a division of Castle Branch, Inc. (the "Company"). Company reserves the right, in its sole discretion, to change, modify, add, or delete portions of this Privacy Policy at any time without further notice and such modifications are, unless otherwise stated in this Privacy Policy, effective immediately. If this Privacy Policy is modified, such changes shall be posted on the Website and Company will make reasonable efforts to bring any modifications to the attention of User at the time of User's access of the Website. User's continued use of the Website after any such changes constitutes User's acceptance of the revised Privacy Policy. If User does not agree to this or any future Privacy Policy, User shall not use or access (or continue to use or access) the Website.

#### Account Registration and Data Collection

Registration of an Account on the Website requires a valid e-mail address and unique password. Company also may collect additional information from User including, but not limited to, legal name, social security number, birth date, address, phone number, and email address, and User shall provide valid, accurate, and complete information as requested and shall keep all registration information complete and current. In addition, when User registers with the Website, Company may ask User for certain additional information and it is within the discretion of User to provide such additional information. User acknowledges and agrees that Company may collect, use, access, disclose, and store User's name, username, password, email address, and any other information (including, without limitation, personally identifiable information) User provides to Company (collectively, "Data") as described and for the purposes set out in the Terms and Conditions of Use for the Website or in this Privacy Policy. A copy of the Terms and Conditions of Use for the Website can be found at https://www.certifiedprofile.com/terms. User also acknowledges and agrees that Company may collect, use, access, disclose, and store User's non-personally identifiable information including IP addresses, profile information, aggregate User data, and browser types in order to manage the Website, track usage, advertise products and services to User, and improve the overall Website.

#### Ownership of Content

User may upload, publish, and display photos, profiles, messages, notes, information, immunization records, transcripts, background reports, documents, records, and other content (collectively, the "Content") on or through the Website, or transmit, disclose, or share the Content with others. User acknowledges and agrees that any party designated by User on the Website may receive, view, obtain, or have access to User's Content and Data. User also may publish, display, transmit, share, or disclose User's Content or Data to any party (including, without limitation, a non-User of the Website). User retains all ownership rights in the Content uploaded, published, entered, or displayed by such User. However, User understands and agrees that Company may, but is not required to, review and delete, without notice, any Content that, in the sole judgment of Company, violates this Privacy Policy or the Terms of Use or which might be offensive, illegal, or that might violate the rights, harm, or threaten the safety of Users or others. Company, regardless of ownership, reserves the right at all times to disclose, in its sole discretion, any Content as authorized or required by any law, regulation, or court order.

**_User understands and agrees that all Content, Data, and other personal information that User supplies to Company will be stored in and accessible from locations within the United States of America, for the purposes set out in the Terms of Use and in this Privacy Policy, and may be subject to production or disclosure requirements by United States authorities in accordance with applicable United States laws._**

#### Account Data and Content Privacy

Company takes the security of User's Data, Content, and other personal information seriously and wants Users to feel comfortable using the Website. Company has implemented industry standard technology designed to keep User Data, Content, and other personal information safe. Company currently employs Secure Socket Layer (SSL) data encryption when data is transmitted over the Internet to the Website. Company's systems are also compliant with the Payment Card Industry Data Security Standard (PCI DSS). Company has installed layered firewalls and other security technologies to help prevent unauthorized access to its systems. Strong password protection protocols are used on all computers and employees are kept up-to-date on Company's security and privacy policies. The servers used to store User information are maintained in a secure environment with appropriate security measures. Company also limits access to personally identifiable information to those employees and contractors who need access in order to carry out their job responsibilities and to certain Educational Institutions (as defined below) or other persons, entities, or organizations designated by User. Such protective measures are designed to limit access to User's Content, Data, and other personal information. Please note that despite Company's efforts, factors beyond Company's control may result in disclosure of User Content, Data, or other personal information. Accordingly, Company is not in a position to guarantee that User information will be secure under all circumstances and Company offers no warranties or representations with regards to the maintenance or non-disclosure of User Content, Data, or other personal information.

#### Use of Data and Content

Company does not disclose, sell, or otherwise transfer User Data or Content except as otherwise set out herein, in the Terms of Use, or as required or permitted by applicable law. Company may disclose, transmit, share, or provide access to User Data and/or Content as follows: (a) as provided in the Terms of Use or this Privacy Policy; (b) pursuant to User's consent, authorization, or designation (for example, when User designates educational institutions, business organizations, or other persons, entities, or organizations to have access to or copies of User's background report, immunization records, Data, Content, or verifications contained within User's Account); (c) to educational institutions and/or departments, institutions, programs, or healthcare facilities or partners affiliated with or a part of such educational institutions (such as hospitals and clinical sites) at which User is enrolled, admitted, employed, being trained, attending instruction or class, serving as an intern, or in a similar position, or applying or being considered for enrollment, admission, employment, training, instruction, internship, or a similar position (collectively, "Educational Institutions"); (d) when a service provided on the Website requires interaction with a third party, or is provided by a third party, such as an application service provider; (e) to Company's agents, employees, or contractors as necessary, in Company's discretion, to perform or provide the products or services requested or purchased by User, such as background reports; (f) as required by law, subpoena, or order of any court or government agency having jurisdiction over Company; or (g) Company or the Website are purchased, in which event the third-party purchaser will have access to and use of the Data and Content in accordance with the Terms of Use and this Privacy Policy.

#### Passwords

All Accounts are password protected. When Users create their Account, Users shall choose a unique username and password. Users shall not disclose their username or password to any third party or permit any third party the use of their username or password. Furthermore, Users are solely responsible for maintaining the confidentiality of their username and password and for any and all activities that occur under that name and password. User shall immediately notify Company if User has any suspicion that an unauthorized party is accessing User's Account. Company will never ask for User's password in an unsolicited phone call or email. User may change his/her password at any time. User is solely liable for all activity, whether or not authorized by User, which occurs under User's Account or password.

#### Right to Delete/Terminate Account

Company, in its sole discretion, may delete User's Account or Data and Content with or without notice or liability to User. Company reserves the right to permanently block any User who violates this Privacy Policy or the Terms of Use. Even after deletion of an Account, Company may retain User Data and Content for archival purposes (as long as reasonable for business or legal purposes). This information is maintained to allow Company to recover Data and Content and restore Accounts in the event of equipment or system failure or to abide by legal requirements.

#### Links

The Website contains links to other websites. Company is not responsible for, and shall have no liability to User with respect to, the privacy policies, terms of use, content, products, services, and/or operations, practices or policies on these other websites. When linking to another website a User should read the terms of use and privacy policy posted on that website. Company's Terms of Use and Privacy Policy only govern Company's Website. When accessing a third-party website via a link, the User is leaving Company's Website and is conducting User's business or other transactions with such other third-party, not with Company.

#### Use of Cookies

Company uses cookies to collect and store User's preferences, usage habits, and record session information. A cookie is a small data file that is transferred to User's hard drive and used for record-keeping purposes. A cookie file can contain information such as the URL, computer IP address, domain type, browser type, the country, state, and telephone area code where User's server is located, the pages of the Website viewed, and any search terms entered on the Website. These cookies allow Company to customize the Website content to User's preferences, profile, and/or demographic information. Company does not link the stored information to any personally identifiable information. Users may configure their browser to accept or reject all or some cookies, or notify User when a cookie is set. Users must enable cookies from Company in order to use most functions on the Website. Please note that Company allows third party advertisers to access cookies on a User's computer. Advertisers' use of cookies is subject to their own privacy policies, not this Privacy Policy.

#### Third Party Advertising

Advertisements may be delivered to User by Company or a third-party company that has an advertising contractual relationship with Company ("Advertiser"). Such Advertisers may set cookies on User's computer to allow the Advertisers to recognize User's computer in the future and store User's preferences. Company and Advertisers may use the cookies to compile information about User. Such information allows Company and Advertisers to deliver targeted advertisements that it or they believe will be of most interest to User. This Privacy Policy covers only Company's cookies, not the use of cookies by any third party Advertisers.

#### Email Choice/Opt-out

User may choose not to receive updates, notifications, Company newsletters, and/or Company advertisements by choosing the appropriate opt-out option in the email containing such newsletter, update, notification, or advertisement. All such updates, notifications, newsletters, and advertisements will also include instructions for opting-out of those communications in the future.

#### International Users

Company may collect, process, and maintain User information in the United States, where privacy laws may not be as protective as in a User's home country. Users using the Website from outside the United States are consenting to the transfer of User's information to the United States for processing and maintaining in a manner consistent with these Terms of Use.

#### Surveys

Company may request User to participate in surveys relating to the Website, Company, or Company's affiliates or third party advertisers. Participation in such surveys is completely voluntary. However, Company encourages User to participate in these surveys as they provide information which will be used to improve the Website. The surveys may request contact information, such as User's name and email address, demographic information, age, or income level. Company, its affiliates and third party advertisers conduct such surveys in order to target advertising and learn User preferences. Company may share the information collected from these surveys with its affiliates, third party advertisers, and the general public, but will not share User's personally identifiable information with any third party without User's prior consent.

#### Contests and Sweepstakes

Company may hold contests, sweepstakes, or other promotions on the Website. Participation in such contests, sweepstakes or other promotions is voluntary and may require entrants to provide personal or contact information. Company will use the information collected to verify the entrant's identity and age and to communicate with entrants. Company will not share any of the entrant's personal or contact information with any third party except to service providers, if any, as disclosed at the time of entry, if User is a contest winner, or as may be required by law. Company may make information about entrants available in aggregated form to advertisers, partners and the general public.

#### Mergers, Acquisitions and Bankruptcy

In the event that Company is acquired by or merged with any third party entity, Company reserves the right, in any of these circumstances, to transfer or assign Users' Content and Data, and the licenses obtained from User for Content and Data, and any information Company has collected from User. In the unlikely event of Company's bankruptcy, insolvency, reorganization, receivership, or assignment for the benefit of creditors, or the application of laws or equitable principles affecting creditors' rights generally, Company may not be able to control how User's personal information is treated, transferred, or used.

## Canadian CertifiedProfile Privacy Policy

This Privacy Policy has been prepared by CertifiedProfile, a division of Castle Branch, Inc. (the "Company"). The Privacy Policy sets out the manner in which the Company collects, uses, discloses and otherwise treats personal information of account (“Account”) holders (registered and nonregistered account holders collectively, “User” or “Users”) and other visitors to Company’s website (the “Website”). If this Privacy Policy is modified, such changes shall be posted on the Website and Company will make reasonable efforts to bring any modifications to the attention of User at the time of User's access of the Website. A copy of the Terms and Conditions of Use for the Website can be found at https://www.certifiedprofile.com/terms.

#### Collection and Use of Personal Information

#### Account Registration and Data Collection

When a User registers an Account on the Website, Company collects certain information, such as a valid e-mail address, username and unique password. Company also may collect additional information from User including, but not limited to, legal name, birth date, address, phone number, email address, designation, degree/certification, and date of graduation. We also collect immunization records, background checks and other information you upload to the site. Registration information is used to provide and otherwise administer the service(s) requested. User shall provide valid, accurate, and complete information as requested and shall keep all registration information complete and current. In addition, when User registers with the Website, Company may ask User for certain additional information and it is within the discretion of User to provide such additional information. User's legal name, username, password, email address, and any other information (including, without limitation, personally identifiable information) provided by User to Company sometimes is referred to herein as the "Data." The content, Data, and information on User's Account, including, but not limited to, any immunization records, background reports, and other documents, records, and information sometimes is referred to herein as the "Content." Company uses the Content for the purposes of assessing the User’s eligibility for clinical practice and otherwise providing and administering the service(s) requested.

#### Surveys

Company may request User to participate in surveys relating to the Website, Company, or Company's affiliates or third party advertisers. Participation in such surveys is completely voluntary. However, Company encourages User to participate in these surveys as they provide information which will be used to improve the Website. The surveys may request contact information, such as User's name and email address, demographic information, age, or income level. Company, its affiliates and third party advertisers conduct such surveys in order to target advertising and learn User preferences. Company may share the information collected from these surveys with its affiliates, third party advertisers, and the general public, but will not share User's personally identifiable information with any third party without User's prior consent.

#### Contests and Sweepstakes

Company may hold contests, sweepstakes, or other promotions on the Website. Participation in such contests, sweepstakes or other promotions is voluntary and may require entrants to provide personal or contact information. Company will use the information collected to verify the entrant's identity and age and to communicate with entrants. Company will not share any of the entrant's personal or contact information with any third party except to service providers, if any, as disclosed at the time of entry, if User is a contest winner, or as may be required by law. Company may make information about entrants available in aggregated form to advertisers, partners and the general public.

#### Website Related Information

Company may collect and use website-related information including IP addresses, aggregate User data (such as page requests and average time spent on the Website), and browser types in order to manage the Website, track usage, advertise products and services to User, and improve the overall Website.

#### Customer Service

When you contact the Company with a comment, question or complaint, you may be asked for information that identifies you (such as your name, address and a phone number) along with additional information we need to help Company promptly answer your question or respond to your comment or complaint. Company may also retain this information to assist you in the future and to improve its customer service, product and service offerings, and events and promotions.

#### Transfer of Data Outside Canada

**_User understands and agrees that all Content, Data, and other personal information that User supplies to Company will be stored in and accessible from locations within the United States of America, for the purposes set out in this Privacy Policy, and may be subject to production or disclosure requirements by United States authorities in accordance with applicable United States laws._**

#### Security of Personal Information

Company takes the security of User's Data, Content, and other personal information seriously and wants Users to feel comfortable using the Website. Company maintains reasonable administrative, technical and physical safeguards in an effort to protect against unauthorized access, use, modification and disclosure of personal information in our custody and control. Company has implemented industry standard technology designed to keep User Data, Content, and other personal information safe. The servers used to store User information are maintained in a secure environment with appropriate security measures. Company also limits access to personally identifiable information to those employees and contractors who need access in order to carry out their job responsibilities. Such protective measures are designed to limit access to User's Content, Data, and other personal information. Please note that despite Company's efforts, factors beyond Company's control may result in disclosure of User Content, Data, or other personal information. Accordingly, Company is not in a position to guarantee that User information will be secure under all circumstances and Company offers no warranties or representations with regards to the maintenance or non-disclosure of User Content, Data, or other personal information.

#### Disclosure of Personal Information

Company does not disclose, trade, rent, sell or otherwise transfer User Data or Content except as set out herein or as otherwise required or permitted by applicable law. Company may disclose, transmit, share, or provide access to User Data and/or Content as follows: (a) as provided in the Terms of Use or this Privacy Policy; (b) pursuant to User's consent, authorization, or designation (for example, when User designates educational institutions, business organizations, or other persons, entities, or organizations to have access to or copies of User's background report, immunization records, Data, Content, or verifications contained within User's Account); (c) to educational institutions and/or departments, institutions, or programs within such educational institutions at which User is admitted, attending instruction or class, or applying or being considered for admission or instruction (collectively, "Educational Institutions"); (d) to Company's agents, employees, or contractors as necessary, in Company's discretion, to perform services on behalf of Company or provide the products or services requested or purchased by User, such as background reports; (e) as required or permitted by applicable law, subpoena, or order of any court or government agency; or (f) Company or the Website are purchased, in which event the third-party purchaser will have access to and use of the Data and Content in accordance with the Terms of Use and this Privacy Policy.

#### Passwords

All Accounts are password protected. When Users create their Account, Users shall choose a unique username and password. Users shall not disclose their username or password to any third party or permit any third party the use of their username or password. Furthermore, Users are solely responsible for maintaining the confidentiality of their username and password and for any and all activities that occur under that name and password. User shall immediately notify Company if User has any suspicion that an unauthorized party is accessing User's Account. Company will never ask for User's password in an unsolicited phone call or email. User may change his/her password at any time. User is solely liable for all activity, whether or not authorized by User, which occurs under User's Account or password.

#### Right to Delete/Terminate Account

Company, in its sole discretion, may delete User's Account or Data and Content with or without notice or liability to User. Company reserves the right to permanently block any User who violates this Privacy Policy or the Terms of Use. Even after deletion of an Account, Company may retain User Data and Content as long as required for business or legal purposes.

#### Retention of Personal Information

We have personal information retention processes designed to retain personal information of Users for no longer than necessary for the purposes stated herein for which it was collected or to otherwise meet legal requirements.

#### Links

The Website contains links to other websites. Company is not responsible for, and shall have no liability to User with respect to, the privacy policies, terms of use, content, products, services, and/or operations, practices or policies on these other websites. When linking to another website a User should read the terms of use and privacy policy posted on that website. Company's Terms of Use and Privacy Policy only govern Company's Website. When accessing a third-party website via a link, the User is leaving Company's Website and is conducting User's business or other transactions with such other third-party, not with Company.

#### Use of Cookies

Company uses cookies to collect and store User's preferences, usage habits, and record session information. A cookie is a small data file that is transferred to User's hard drive and used for record-keeping purposes. A cookie file can contain information such as the URL, computer IP address, domain type, browser type, the country, state, and telephone area code where User's server is located, the pages of the Website viewed, and any search terms entered on the Website. These cookies allow Company to customize the Website content to User's preferences, profile, and/or demographic information. Company does not link the stored information to any personally identifiable information. Users may configure their browser to accept or reject all or some cookies, or notify User when a cookie is set. Users must enable cookies from Company in order to use most functions on the Website. Please note that Company allows third party advertisers to access cookies on a User's computer. Advertisers' use of cookies is subject to their own privacy policies, not this Privacy Policy.

#### Third Party Advertising

Advertisements may be delivered to User by Company or a third-party company that has an advertising contractual relationship with Company ("Advertiser"). Such Advertisers may set cookies on User's computer to allow the Advertisers to recognize User's computer in the future and store User's preferences. Company and Advertisers may use the cookies to compile information about User. Such information allows Company and Advertisers to deliver targeted advertisements that it or they believe will be of most interest to User. This Privacy Policy covers only Company's cookies, not the use of cookies by any third party Advertisers.

#### Email Choice/Opt-out

From time to time, Company may collect certain personal information (such as first and last name and email address) to send you updates, notifications, Company newsletters, and/or Company advertisements. You may opt-out of receiving such communications by choosing the appropriate opt-out option in the email containing such newsletter, update, notification, or advertisement or by contacting us as set out below.

#### International Users

Company may collect, process, and maintain User information in the United States, where privacy laws may not be as protective as in a User's home country. Users using the Website from outside the United States are consenting to the transfer of User's information to the United States for processing and maintaining in a manner consistent with these Terms of Use.

#### Mergers, Acquisitions and Bankruptcy

In the event that all or part of the Company is acquired by or merged with any third party entity, or in the unlikely event of the Company’s bankruptcy, insolvency, reorganization, receivership or assignment, Company may transfer or assign Users' Content and Data, and the licenses obtained from User for Content and Data, and any information Company has collected from User.

#### Access to Your Personal Information

You have the right to access, update, and correct inaccuracies in your personal information in Company’s custody and control, subject to certain exceptions prescribed by law. In order to update your username and/or password, you will need to select Account Settings in your CertifiedProfile Account. You may request access, updating and corrections of inaccuracies in other personal information in Company’s custody or control by emailing or writing to Company at the contact information set out below. Company may request certain personal information for the purposes of verifying the identity of the individual seeking access to their personal information records.

#### Changes to the Privacy Policy

This Privacy Policy may be updated periodically to reflect changes to our personal information practices. The revised Privacy Policy will be posted on the Websites. We strongly encourage you to refer to this Privacy Policy often for the latest information about our personal information practices.

#### Contact Us

Please contact the Company if you have any questions or comments about this Privacy Policy, if you wish to access, update, and/or correct inaccuracies in your personal information, or if you otherwise have a question or complaint about the manner in which we or our service providers treat your personal information. You may contact the Company at (888) 914-7279 or [cpservicedesk@certifiedprofile.com](mailto:cpservicedesk@certifiedprofile.com).

For your convenience, CertifiedProfile is available as a mobile application and web-based hub.
